Guide to the Stanford German Student Association Records SC1208
Dept. of Special Collections & University Archives
Stanford German Student Association records
1997-2014
SC1208
Dept. of Special Collections & University Archives
411.0 megabyte(s) (462 files in 34 folders)
Organizational HIstory
The Stanford German Student Association was founded in 1997 to provide a forum for Stanford affiliates with an interest in German language and culture.
Scope and Contents
Includes correspondence, reports, minutes, flyers, and other materials created by the Stanford German Student Association, a volunteer student organization at Stanford University, from its founding in 1997 until 2014. Also includes digital photographs of events held for visiting dignitaries including Helmut Schmidt (2000) and Angela Merkel (2010).
Access to Collection
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
College students--California--Stanford.; German language--Study and teaching.; Stanford University--Students.
- Documents, 2003-2012
- Event posters, 2006-2014
- Event photographs, 2000-2013
  - Schmidt, Helmut, 2000; 1.0 computer file(s) (JPG)
  - Feuerzangenbowle, 2006; 21.0 computer file(s) (JPG)
  - Kamingespraech, 2006-2007; 39.0 computer file(s) (JPG)
  - Sommerfest, 2007-05-13; 51.0 computer file(s) (JPG)
  - Oktoberfest, 2007-10-26; 64.0 computer file(s) (JPG)
  - Merkel, Angela, 2010-04-15; 69.0 computer file(s) (JPG)
  - Besuch, Roesler, 2011-02-11; 11.0 computer file(s) (JPG)
  - Feuerzangenbowle, 2011-12-03; 19.0 computer file(s) (JPG)
  - Oktoberfest, 2012-10-07; 39.0 computer file(s) (JPG)
  - Gottschalk, 2013-04-30; 47.0 computer file(s) (JPG)
- Event Videorecordings, 2007
  - John Ernest Foundation, 2007-07; 1.0 computer file(s) (MPG)
- Website files, 1999-2008
  - Webserver backup, 1999-2007
  - Webserver backup, 1999-2008